The team maintains possession with a pass.
Fans on both sides making themselves heard.
Carlos Mendez with a clever pass to Liam Johnson.
The managers will be pleased with the effort shown.
Liam Johnson with a searching ball into the box.
The tempo of the match has been excellent.
Action from Barnsley.
This has been an entertaining encounter.
It's a corner for Barnsley.
The pace of the game has slowed down a bit now.
Thomas Baker delivers a cross into the box.
Kevin Zhang finds Alejandro Fernandez with a good pass.
We're seeing some good movement off the ball.
Action from Barnsley.
The conditions are perfect for football today.
It's a corner for Barnsley.
Both teams are well-organized defensively.
Action from Barnsley.
The managers will be pleased with the effort shown.
Michael Peterson makes a good run with possession.